通過。
根據藥劑業及毒藥條例，就批准《二零一三年藥劑業及毒藥修訂》。
第六號規例及二零一三年讀入表修訂第六號規例而動議嘅疑決議案。
有意就議案發言嘅議員，請按下要求發言嘅按鈕。現在我請食物及衞生局局長發言及動議議案。食物及衞生局局長。
主席，我 move that the motion under my name, as printed on the agenda, be passed.
目前，我們規ulate the sale and supply of pharmaceutical products.
Through a registration monitoring system set up in accordance with the Pharmacy and Poisons Ordinance.
The ordinance maintains several schedules under the Pharmacy and Poisons Regulations and Poisons List under the Poisons List Regulations.
藥品產品，put under different parts of the poison list.
and different schedules are subject to different levels of control, in order in regard to the conditions of sale and keeping of warehouse.
for protection of public health, some pharmaceutical products can only be sold in pharmacies under supervision of registered pharmacists.
and， in their presence。
For certain pharmaceutical products, proper records of particulars of the sale must be kept, including the date of sale, the name and address of the purchaser, the name and quantity of medicine and the purpose for which it is required.
The sale of some pharmaceutical products must be authorised by prescription from a registered medical practitioner, dentist or veterinary surgeon.
rising from an application for registration of two pharmaceutical products, the pharmacy and poison spot proposed.
to add the following substance to part one of the poisons list.
And first and third schedules to the Pharmacy Importants Regulations.
A, mirabegron， is sourced。
是esters，their source。
And B.
黑社會派，是 source。
The pharmaceutical products containing the above two substances must then be sold in pharmacies under supervision of registered pharmacies and in their presence, with the support of prescriptions.
For amendment regulations concerning the adding of the above substance to Part One of the Poisons List and the first and third schedules to the Farming Poisons Regulations.
We propose them to take immediate effect.
The point gets settled on the 29 November.
2013。
to allow early control and sale of the relevant medicine.
The two amendment regulations are made by the Pharmacy and Poisons Board, which is a statutory authority established under the ordinance to regulate pharmaceutical products.
The port comprises members engaged in pharmacy, medical and academic professions.
The board considers the proposed amendments necessary in view of the potency, toxicity and potential side effects of the medicines concerned.
With these remarks, Ms. President, I hope members could support the motion. Thank you.
我現在向各位提出嘅第二議題係食物衞生局局長動議嘅議案，予以通過。有冇議員想發言？
我現在向各位提出嘅代決議題係食物及衞生局局長動議嘅議案，予以通過。現在付諸表決，贊成嘅請舉手。
反對嘅請舉手。
我認為議題獲得在席議員以過半數贊成，我宣佈議案獲得通過。